https://avn.com/about-us/privacy-policy.html

-->
All models were at least 18 years old at the time of their performance. 18 U.S.C. 2257 Record-Keeping Requirements Compliance Statement.
Subscribe
AVN.com and its subsidiary websites, as well as show websites are an AVN Media Network, Inc. site. In protecting your privacy we are providing this statement detailing our online data practices and the options you have about the way your data is collected and used on these AVN Media Network, Inc. sites.
Collecting Data
Only persons who provide us with the requested unique user specific data will be able to order programs, services and products or otherwise participate in the site's activities and programs. Non-unique user data may be collected when you visit many of our site pages such as the kind of browser you are using (e.g., Netscape, Internet Explorer, Mozilla Firefox), the kind of operating system you are using, (e.g., Windows 2000 or Mac OS) and the domain name of your Internet service provider (e.g., America Online, MSN).
Data Usage
We may use the data you provide about yourself to complete your requests for our programs, services and products, to address your inquiries about our programs, and to offer you other products, programs or services that might be of interest to you. We sometimes use this data to communicate with you, such as to notify you when you have won one of our contests, to fulfill a request by you for an online newsletter, or to contact you about your business with us. We sometimes use the non-unique user specific data that we collect to improve the design and content of our site and to enable us to personalize your online activities. We also may use this data to analyze site usage, as well as to offer you programs, services or products. We may disclose unique user specific data in response to legal obligations, for example, in response to a court order or a subpoena. We also may disclose such data in response to a law enforcement agency's request. Agents and contractors of AVN Media Network, Inc. who have access to unique user specific data are required to protect this data in a way that is consistent with this Privacy Policy, for example, not using the data for any purpose other than to complete the services they are handling for AVN Media Network, Inc.
Although we take appropriate steps to protect against unauthorized disclosures of data, we cannot guarantee you that unique user specific data that we collect will never be disclosed in a manner that is inconsistent with this Privacy Policy. Occasionally we may combine data we acquire online with other records to enhance our ability to market to you those products or services that may be of interest to you. If you prefer not to receive marketing information from this site, please email [email protected] to submit your request. AVN Media Network, Inc. sites covered by this Privacy Policy will not use or distribute unique user specific data provided to us in ways unrelated to the ones detailed above without also providing you with an opportunity to opt out of these unrelated uses.
Collection of Data by Strategic Partner Sites and Sponsors Links on our sites may direct you to other sites and their information policies and privacy guidelines may differ from ours. Please read the privacy statements on other sites as we have no control over what these strategic partner sites do with your data collected and/or submitted. The AVN Media Network, Inc. sites covered by this Privacy Statement sometimes may offer programs (e.g., contests, sweepstakes, or promotions) that are sponsored by or co-branded with identified strategic partners. The strategic partners may obtain unique user specific data that visitors voluntarily submit to participate in the programs. AVN Media Network, Inc. has no control over these strategic partners' use of this data.
Unsubscribe
In the event you are receiving communications from AVN Media Network, Inc. and wish to no longer receive these communications you can unsubscribe at any time by clicking on the unsubscribe link at the bottom of the communication or alternatively you may send an email to [email protected] with the request. Please include any pertinent information such as name, email address, and/or physical address.  Alternatively you may also send an unsubscribe request by physical mail to: AVN Media Network, Inc. c/o Subscriptions, 9400 Penfield Ave, Chatsworth, CA 91311 with the name, email address and/or physical address with which you would like removed from our distribution list.
Cookies
To better understand our site traffic, many of our Internet pages use "cookies" to track user experience. Cookies are text files placed in your computer's browser. Cookies do not tell us your e-mail address or other unique user specific data unless you choose to provide this data to us by, for example, registering at one of our sites. However, once you choose to furnish the site with unique user specific data, this data may be built into the cookie. We use cookies to understand site usage and to improve the content and programs on our sites. For example, we may use cookies to personalize your experience at our web pages (e.g., to recognize you by name when you return to our site) or to save your password in password-protected areas. We also may use cookies to offer you programs, services or products. Security Commitment We have implemented appropriate physical, electronic, and managerial procedures to protect and help prevent unauthorized access, control data security, and properly use the data collected online.
Data Changes
For instructions on how you can access the unique user specific data that this AVN Media Network, Inc. site has collected about you online, or how to correct factual errors in such data, please contact us at [email protected]. To protect your privacy and security, we will take reasonable steps to help verify your identity before granting access or making corrections.
Contact Information
If you have any questions or concerns about the AVN Media Network, Inc. online policy for this site or its implementation you may contact us at www.avnmedianetwork.com.
Copyright © 2020 AVN Media Network |
2257 Notice |
Privacy Policy
| Request Desktop Version
| Request Mobile Version
